▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第三轮
高芙 6-1 7-6(3) 李吉妮 · 赛后场上采访
She managed to find a way
她想办法找到了突破口
to regain control and wrap up the win.
重新掌控局面 锁定胜利
straight sets, but not straightforward.
直落两盘 但绝不轻松
6-1, 7-6(3)
6-1 7-6(3)
Then you flipped the switch
然后你像换了个开关一样
and changed things up and made sure
整个打法都变了 而且确保
that you walked off the court today
今天最后是
in straight sets.
直落两盘走下场的
Tell us how you did it.
说说你是怎么做到的？
Yeah. I mean she started to play better.
是啊 她后来打得更好了
I had a couple break opportunities
我有过几个破发点
in a second.
在第二盘
So just trying
所以就是尽量
to to forget those the ones that I missed.
把没把握住的那几个忘掉
And honestly, it was really hard
说实话 今天真的很难
to control the ball today.
控制住球
I think we're both making a lot
我们俩今天可能都
of unforced errors
犯了不少非受迫失误
that maybe we both normally don't make,
平时都不太会犯的那种
but it was my first time playing
不过这是我今年第一次
on center court this year.
在这片中心球场打球
So happy to be back here on this court.
能回到这片场地上真的很开心
We love having you back.
我们也很高兴你回来
So often we see in women's tennis now,
女子网坛现在常常是
go big or go home, but you weren't afraid
要么全力搏杀 要么什么都不是
to mix things up a little bit today.
但你今天不怕把打法变一变
You got up to the net when you had to.
该上网的时候你就上了
What are you happiest
这场表现里
with about your performance?
你最满意哪一点？
Yeah,
嗯
I think just staying mentally solid even
我觉得是心态一直稳得住
if I wasn't, you know, feeling the ball
哪怕到第二盘
so good towards the second set.
手感其实没那么好
But you know, also I had some doubles
而且我发球也出现了几个双误
on the serve, but you know,
不过
I thought I serve aggressively
我发球还是打得很主动
and yeah, I think you know,
而且
playing from a night match to the day,
从夜场打到白天
it's so different, so just trying to adjust
感觉完全不一样 我就是在适应
with that.
这种变化
Okay, last question.
好 最后一个问题
You said you weren't feeling the ball.
你说手感不太好
Were you feeling the love
那有没有感受到
from everybody here in Cincinnati?
辛辛那提这边的爱？
Yes, for sure.
当然有
Definitely impossible not to to feel
根本不可能感受不到
the love.
这份爱
And yeah, the lady
对了 那位
who started the chant and the tiebreaker.
在抢七带头喊口号的女士
I I enjoyed that one.
我很喜欢那一下
So, thank you.
谢谢大家
So, you noticed it.
看来你注意到了
Way to go. Through to the fourth round.
太棒了 晋级第四轮
Coco Gauff, everybody.
高芙 掌声送给她
This is awesome.
太精彩了